three-two-one oh yeah I got it right now
in your mouth all right do the glue do
the Glock I'm gonna give you all c'mon
and I'm gonna die happy joy please what
would you like for your last meal like
sushi maybe wash it down with a little
IPA oh my god little sushi little IPA
you kidding me you are oh who remembers
going anywhere Oh sushi fish rice etc
and so much more than that today we're
having a special guest here
welcome everybody cheered leaves yes so
before we dive into the food etc I want
to get you in kind of the mindset of
death I'm thinking about that okay -
close your eyes okay and just like try
to be present in thinking about death
mm-hmm think about your death think
about you know maybe if you have any
like pets that you love I did accept the
death of my cat cuz she jumped off my
balcony and I didn't see her so I
thought she got taken by a hawk because
I heard that happens by where I live
and then um and then she came upstairs
so she's fine
so this is the story about like your cat
that's like fine so you're in the end
your cat's not dead nope okay so why
don't we actually just stay present in
the thoughts of death here
cool all right you asked for sushi in
the night PA first thing we got to do
this is rice you ever seen before
yeah a couple a marui so want something
that's special about sushi rice is you
actually season it with some stuff so
this is rice wine vinegar made from rice
alcohol okay
so you just put a bunch of that you want
to make it sweet add some sugar a little
bit of salt now we're just gonna
freaking dissolve this and then we're
gonna kind of stir it into our rice chop
it in the real question is are you
afraid of that kind of I got their moods
where I wake up and I'm like I'm gonna
get hit by a car today okay oh you're
afraid of like dying I think like while
someone was like stabbing me in places
that weren't actually gonna kill me if
they were drowning me then they'd bring
me back up give me once to have and them
yeah yeah and then they plop doing the
fire a puppy and find a guy like right
when you think you're gonna be that you
know this is how I go they put you right
back into the water
yeah and water soldered way thicker now
it's almost like jello then they bring
me up and they kind of like I don't know
rip your skin off they said it's like
I'll flake like you were gyro meat so
this is like kind of pretty similar to
what fish go through before they yeah
yeah you fish if you fish differently
you all the hell Cheers
god bless you do a little two second
show yeah okay we got to do we got to
start seasoning this rice here yeah I
want you to just pour it while I cut the
rice base so I'm just cutting it okay
you're like slice it yes you don't want
to smush her so basically I'm gonna I'm
just gonna get this little damp paper
towel so it doesn't dry out while we're
doing the other stuff we're gonna make
some shrimp tempura some condiments some
spice Mayo sabi and then we're gonna cut
up our fish and start assembling some
sushi and then after that you die yeah
we're gonna start with the eggs give the
egg a crack fresh is all goddamn hell by
the way how do you have I gonna need
like how old do you think you're gonna
be when you die I thought I was gonna
die this year really yeah why oh no I
just have this intuition I'm gonna get
hit by a car do you cross a lot of
streets how fast no like seems so easy
like you're just like standing the
sidewalk and someone likes oh my god hey
that's really tough I mean at least now
that if that happens you've like totally
cold yeah I just bubble I would be cool
okay I want you to slowly pour that
water in here
this is ice water you want to keep
everything cold we don't wanna get the
ice in sand we don't wanna get the ice
in sand we don't wanna get the ice in so
maybe your fingers over okay there we go
okay so we're basically putting you want
to put a cup of water a cup of flour
that looks like it's a cup of flour
maybe huh yeah you ever knowing it
shrimp tambour they're so goddamn long
yeah yeah basically what you do is you
give them a bunch of little slits here
so then what you do is you basically
just squish the goddamn living bejesus
out of it all right little smoosh
something I didn't realize is that
shrimp have a lot of like poop goop and
they're little in their little hand
Chandler's here accidentally ate one of
those before
what the poop dude the goop squad we can
put these little bad boys in some flour
here just give him a nice little dusting
we start to fry these up yeah okay this
one gets dunker rude like this okay it's
all coated hey what do you think happens
after you die I would hope something I
would hope that one day we could see
each other again you a nun embrace yes
my god dude we doesn't matter kidding me
okay I think these are good those are
quick shrimp tempura huh that looks good
yes the man if you want these are all
our little Krispies you know a Newcomb
more little Krispies okay and you can
just like have a little crunch aru's
some of the crunchiest things i've ever
seen yeah you could probably put some
powdered sugar on here and call the
carnival so for everyone this is
Japanese mail it comes with a little
star shape under it so you can squish
out little stars just in case that's
cute
not so bad spicy sauce this is you will
never be able to tell what brand this is
I'll tell you what you can't find it the
shit's rare is all goddamn hell ain't no
one getting suit today everybody curtain
flirted herb little gloop in there it's
all very casual yech wasabi
uh not really cool he's like we're just
gonna make a little bit then okay I
think we're about almost ready to start
making our sushi let's do it which is
kind of mad you the first thing gonna do
is in a Giri basically the principle is
this you lay the fish over here over the
what they called in this video from
Japan I saw the root of your fingers
major that was pretty funny that's the
fingers so then you get a little kind of
like tiny little golf ball you don't
want to squish it down push it down no
no it's like Lucy when I have some like
air in between what you do is you plop
that guy right in there and there's two
things that you can do one is this you
squish it like that and the other one is
squishing it like that and then I saw
someone online go like this they went to
earth and they flop it and then they
bring it back and then once they've
flopped it then they start they start
jumping and start blinking it and start
but duking it gives Erica chunking
little jump really
alright see Babs you follow along with
me alright what do you want your funeral
will be like if you could you could plan
your funeral like what homies are coming
who's not invited I don't want any
stupid kids there like I don't know kids
are out but what if you have kids or
your kids gonna be like um yeah yeah I
just don't want like 500,000 stupid kids
running around being annoying right all
everyone's saying horrible things about
me on the podium
well it's gonna be like a roast like
what are you worried people want people
to roast me a little bit I'll be fun I
think those are done let's move on to
another kind of sushi right now we're
making a classic roll that you'd find it
in
yeah at a sushi place we got the rice on
the outside it's company can inside out
sort of roll here so here we got
cucumbers here we've got tiny little
fishy eggs here we got bigger bigger
fishy so this is like a billion like
dead fish tiny potential fish there I'm
gonna put this SME seeds on here so
basically I spread out this rice thin
and then I'm gonna in just give it a
little blessing yeah
just bless all the hell speaking of hell
what would your personal hell look like
it's like being stuck in an elevator
it's like humid and you're with like
your five least favorite people doing a
guy that would be who's my least
favourite people who are yours my least
favorite people Marc Jacob Chris Diane
and Craig you guys yeah then okay okay
so I so now we got rice on the outside
we got avocado we got shrimp tempura now
you gotta watch this carefully all right
I'm really bad at this what we're gonna
do here is they're gonna we're gonna
they're gonna flip it over all right
make sure you're watching I'm so bad at
this all right hey watching yeah okay
God don't tell me don't tell me how bad
I am all right because we're trying to
flip it over all right
you're watching this yeah okay all right
okay then we're just gonna have to just
gonna have to so you basically we're
halfway there
don't look away don't look away keep
your eyes on so and then we're gonna
roll it forward and that's gonna make
the connection okay
BAM but you think you're done I'm so bad
at this but this is I know this is how
you're supposed to do it this is the
worst part have you ever rolled the
joint before it no yeah me either so I'm
giving this little scooter answers
it's not who knows hey it doesn't look
too bad it looks a little squished
it's not completely closed and that's or
something that happens sometimes when
you make sous-chefs just life it doesn't
work entirely it doesn't but then you
just hide the crease right you hide the
crease exactly BAM what's gonna happen
no problem and then it's making it all
cute so basically right here we got got
salmon avocado tuna avocado salmon on
top and then I think basically you just
you want to give it again you're
watching yeah I'm watching so good so
I'm gonna try to cut this I'm just so
bad at this it could always be better
that's what my my mom used to say that's
what she said about sometimes oh okay
cool
let's plate this sucker up I think I'm
probably gonna like do like spicy mayo
it's already on there well there we go
yeah that's not horrible not amazing but
somewhere in between yeah honestly not
so terribly bad sorry guys I forgot to
bless this with some freaking crispy
bits yeah that's what they are I've seen
those little crispy boys this is kind of
like if Taco Bell made a sushi kind of
thing here okay take one of these bad
boys something here's an actual piece of
information you guys can use you usually
want to put the rice on the rough side
of the nori so shiny rough you can see
the rough has more texture to it I kind
of want you to fling a fish ball in the
air and catch it or me catch it I want
this to happen for you so I'm just gonna
give you the know yet the fling you know
no no yes no my children okay give it a
little I'm gonna smoosh it here so
basically this is the top your hand roll
that's the bottom of your hand roll just
so you have it in your mind okay and if
you ever feeling stuck just grab a
little Skoosh then pickle you want I'm
gonna put some of this in their
kids ah bu cumber we heard nobody you
give a little crunch I'm putting little
crunches for safekeeping so imagine a
cone right yes you're trying to like
kind of get this go over like that okay
better than yours actually no when it
kind of looks cute
no that's cuz you were watching you so
closely earlier alright oh my god dude
that's some sushi you verse the guy she
tells you not to worry about yeah so um
we don't exactly have like a table here
for you but I'd like you to get inside
here if you don't mind
sure oh my gosh hey be careful so take a
look at what we've made her today
I mean we've gotten a Giri both salmon
and tuna looking absolutely delicious
we've got han role that we've
personalized and then we've got shrimp
tempura and a shrimp tempura kind of
crunchy sort of roll with the spicy mayo
a bunch of bunch of boys on there
avocado and various fishes on top and
you got your IPA here Road beer if
you're gonna use the soy sauce maybe
take a look like bend over a little bit
cuz this coffin is a rental yeah take a
nice little bite
we would love to give you the chance now
that you've had your final your last
meal here to give us your last words to
camera so we just when they give you the
opportunity to kind of like say you're a
new one yeah for sure absolutely yeah so
yeah when you go ahead and tell me your
your last words there we go a big one
that was a big one
cool oh no damn it sorry brother oh man
enjoy your right behave off get amazing
to talk to you have to make this last
forever yeah good luck there's not a
whole see at home it seems complicated
but it's totally not and make the rice
you know season the rice get all your
ingredients way it is and I really
encourage you to try at home just make
sure you get nice fish and that's all
that matters and remember nothing tastes
better then your last meal hi everyone
it's me Chad Lee's and I'll be here all
week with Comedy Central make sure to
drop a comment if you're from my channel
you little freaks